A Guide to the Papers of William B. Spong, 1965-1974
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Legislative
  - Commerce - Consumer - Fish Inspection (S. 1092) 1969 (Box 13)
  - Commerce - Consumer - National Institute of Advertising, Marketing and Society 1972 (Box 13)
  - Commerce - Consumer - Pay T.V. 1969, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - Commerce - Consumer - Poison Prevention Packaging Act 1969 (Box 13)
  - Commerce - Consumer - Product Safety Act (S. 983) 1972 (Box 13)
  - Commerce - Consumer - Product Warranty Bill, S. 986 1971, 3 folders (Box 13)
  - Commerce - Consumer Protection Agency 1972 Feb (Box 13)
  - Commerce - Consumer Protection Agency 1972 Mar-Nov, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Consumer - Regulation of Trade in Drugs Acts, S. 1575 & S. 2749 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Daylight Savings Time 1968 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Door to Door Sales 1968 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Energy - El Paso Natural Gas Company Merger 1972 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Energy - Energy Crisis 1972 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Energy - Federal Power Commission Procedures 1967 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Energy - Natural Energy Resources Advisory Board (S. 3641) 1972 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Energy - Natural Gas Pipeline Safety Bill (S. 1166) 1967 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Energy - Natural Resources 1969-1970 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Energy - Power Plant Siting 1971-1972 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Energy - Power Plant Siting - Hearings 1972 (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Environment 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Commerce- Environment - Coastal Zone Management Bills, S. 582 & S. 3507 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Environment - Detergents 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Environment - Endangered Species 1969 & 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Commerce - Environment - Endangered Species - Whales (S.J.Res. 115) 1971 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Environment - Environmental Protection Act, S. 1302 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Environment - Environmental Protection Act, S. 1302 - "Michigan's Environmental Protection Act of 1970: A Progress Report" [1972], 2 folders (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Environment - Federal Wildlife Restoration Act (S. 670) 1969-1970 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Environment - National Emission Standards 1970 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Environment - Non-Returnable Containers (S. 1377) 1971-1972 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Environment - Non-Returnable Containers (Petitions) 1971 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Environment - Pesticides 1972 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Environment - Safe Drinking Water Act (S. 3994) 1972 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Environment - Toxic Substances 1971-1972, 5 folders (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Fair Credit Billing (S. 652) 1972 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Federal Insurance Guaranty Bill (S. 2236) 1969-1970 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Food Supplements 1967-1968, 1972 (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Horse Protection 1967-1971, 4 folders (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Merchant Marine and Fisheries 1967-1968, 3 folders (Box 15)
  - Commerce - Merchant Marine and Fisheries 1969-1972, 7 folders (Box 16)
  - Commerce - Merchant Marine and Fisheries - Delta Queen 1970 (Box 16)
  - Commerce - Merchant Marine and Fisheries - Maritime Authority Bill 1972, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Commerce - Merchant Marine and Fisheries - Oil Import Bill (H.R. 13324) 1972 (Box 16)
  - Commerce - Merchant Marine and Fisheries - Sale of Passenger Ships 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 16)
  - Commerce - Merchant Marine and Fisheries - Shipbuilding (S. 2148) 1969-1970 (Box 16)
  - Commerce - Metric System 1971-1972 (Box 16)
  - Commerce - No Fault 1970-1972 Jul, 11 folders (Box 16)
  - Commerce - No Fault 1972 Aug-Dec, 4 folders (Box 17)
  - Commerce - Ocean Mammals, S. 2871 1972, 4 folders (Box 17)
  - Commerce - Ocean Mammals - Dolphins 1972 (Box 17)
  - Commerce - Ocean Mammals - Harris-Pryor Bill 1972 (Box 17)
  - Commerce - Ocean Mammals - Seals 1972 (Box 17)
  - Commerce - Oceanography 1969-1972, 3 folders (Box 17)
  - Commerce - St. Lawrence Seaway (S. 3137) 1969-1970 (Box 17)
  - Commerce - SST [Supersonic Transport]- Appropriations 1966, 1968-1970, 10 folders (Box 17)
  - Commerce - SST [Supersonic Transport]-Appropriations 1971, 7 folders (Box 18)
  - Commerce - SST [Supersonic Transport]- Appropriations - Pro 1970-1971, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation 1967-1972, 14 folders (Box 18)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - ASTRO [America's Sound Transportation Review Organization ] Study 1971, 9 folders (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Attorney Fee Recovery, S.858 & S. 1653 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Barge Mixing 1970 (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Freight Forwarders (S. 1896) 1971 (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Hours of Service Bill (S. 1938) 1969 (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - ICC and Livestock Shipments (S. 748) 1969 (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Motor Carrier Rates (S. 2245) 1970 (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Penn Central 1970 (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Railroads 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Railroad Bill, H.R. 13300 1969-1970, 3 folders (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Railroad Reimbursement (S. 2750) 1970 (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - Railroad Safety Act 1968-1971 (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Surface Transportation - S. Con. Res. 25 1967-1968 (Box 19)
  - Commerce - Textiles 1967 & 1969 (Box 19)
  - District of Columbia 1967-1972, 10 folders (Box 20)
  - District of Columbia - Abortion 1970 (Box 20)
  - District of Columbia - Adoption Amendment 1970 (Box 20)
  - District of Columbia - Air Pollution 1967 (Box 20)
  - District of Columbia - Air Pollution - Northern Virginia 1967 (Box 20)
  - District of Columbia - Airports - Dulles & National 1967-1972, 14 folders (Box 20)
  - District of Columbia - Airports - Dulles & National ca. 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Alcoholic Beverage Control Act 1967-1970 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Appropriations 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Budget Fiscal 1969 1967-1968 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Business and Commerce 1967-1968, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - City Council 1967 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Committee Agenda 1967-1968, 12 folders (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Committee Chair 1970 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Committee Handouts 1967 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Commuter Tax 1968-1971 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Conservation and Water Supply 1967-1969 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Council on Government 1967 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Credit Card Fraud 1970 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Crime 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Crime Bill 1970, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Crime in Schools 1969-1970 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Court Reorganization 1969 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Education 1967-1970, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Education - Federal City College 1967-1969 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Education - Washington International School 1969 (Box 21)
  - District of Columbia - Fiscal Affairs 1966-1970 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Fiscal Affairs - Policemen, Firemen, & Teachers Pay Bill 1967-1970, 7 folders (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Fiscal Affairs - Potomac Interceptor 1967 & n.d., 4 folders (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Fiscal Affairs - Revenue Hearings 1967, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Government Reorganization 1967, 4 folders (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Healing Arts Practice Act 1969 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Home Rule 1965-1971 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Implied Consent 1969 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - International Center 1967 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Judgeship 1970 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Judiciary 1968 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Landfills & Solid Waste Disposal 1967-1970 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Limitations on Building Claims (H.R. 6527) 1968 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Lorton Reformatory Transfer 1970 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Media Tax 1969 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Medical Schools (S. 3974) 1970 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Mentally Retarded Persons 1969 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Methadone 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Minimum Drinking Age 1968 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Minimum Wage 1969 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - National Capital Housing 1969-1971 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - National Capital Planning Commission 1967 (Box 22)
  - District of Columbia - Parking Problems & Bill 1968-1972 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Police & Fire Departments - Retirement 1967-1971 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Potomac River (S. 3717) 1970 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Prince William County Land Bill 1968-1971 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Psychology Practice Regulations 1969 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Public Health, Education, Welfare & Safety 1967-1972, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Revenue Bill 1968-1971, 2 folders (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - St. Elizabeth's Hospital Proposed Transfer 1969 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Statute of Limitations 1967-1969 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Tax on Professionals 1968 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Tiber Island 1969 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Transportation 1966-1972, 7 folders (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Transportation - Seaplane Shuttle 1969 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Walter Washington - Nomination for Commissioner 1967 (Box 23)
  - District of Columbia - Worker's Compensation 1969 (Box 23)
  - Finance 1966-1972, 7 folders (Box 23)
  - Finance - Budget, Status of 1968 (Box 24)
  - Finance - Campaign Financing 1966-1968, 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Finance - Community Self-Determination Bill (Research) 1968 Jun (Box 24)
  - Finance - Debt Limit Increase 1967, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Finance - Guaranteed Annual Income 1967-1968 (Box 24)
  - Finance - Government Spending 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 24)
  - Finance - Imports 1967-1971, 7 folders (Box 24)
  - Finance - Imports - Burke-Hartke Bill, S. 2592 1972, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Finance - Imports - Meats 1967-1971 (Box 25)
  - Finance - Imports - Shoes 1967-1971 (Box 25)
  - Finance - Imports - Steel 1967-1971 (Box 25)
  - Finance - Imports - Textiles 1965-1971, 6 folders (Box 25)
  - Finance - Inflation 1969-1972, 4 folders (Box 25)
  - Finance - Inflation - Ceiling Price List 1971 (Box 25)
  - Finance - Inflation - Excise Tax 1971 (Box 25)
  - Finance - Inflation - Investment Tax Credit 1971 (Box 25)
  - Finance - Inflation - Teachers' Salary Increase (H.R. 11309) 1971 Aug-Oct (Box 25)
  - Finance - Inflation - Teachers' Salary Increase (H.R. 11309) 1971 Nov-1972 (Box 26)
  - Finance - Inflation - Wage Price Freeze 1971-1972, 7 folders (Box 26)
  - Finance - Internal Revenue 1967 (Box 26)
  - Finance - Pensions Plan (S. 3598) 1972 (Box 26)
  - Finance - Re-negotiation Act 1968 (Box 26)
  - Finance - Revenue Sharing 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box 26)
  - Finance - Rural Job Development Act (S. 15) 1969 (Box 26)
  - Finance - Social Security 1967, 5 folders (Box 26)
  - Finance - Social Security (Form Letter Reply) 1967 (Box 26)
  - Finance - Social Security 1968-1972, 6 folders (Box 27)
  - Finance - Social Security - Amendment H.R. 1 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box 27)
  - Finance - Social Security - Amendment H.R. 1 - Adoption of Amendment 411 1970-1972 (Box 27)
  - Finance - Social Security - Amendment H.R. 1 - Chiropractors 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 27)
  - Finance - Social Security - Amendment H.R. 1 - Church Amendment #999 1972 (Box 27)
  - Finance - Social Security - Amendment H.R. 1 - Family Assistance Plan 1969-1970 Sep, 3 folders (Box 27)
  - Finance - Social Security - Amendment H.R. 1 - Family Assistance Plan 1970 Oct-1972, 7 folders (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Amendment H.R. 1 - Medicredit 1970-1971 (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Amendment H.R. 1 - Ribicoff Amendment 1972 (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Amendment H.R. 1 - Section 232 1971 (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Bennett Amendment 1970 (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Children & Youth Program 1971 (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Disability for the Blind 1969 (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Earning Limitations & Benefits 1967-1972, 6 folders (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Long Amendment 1970 (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Medicare & Medicaid 1967-1969, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Finance - Social Security - Medicare & Medicaid 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 29)
  - Finance - Social Security - National Health Care Plan 1970-1972, 5 folders (Box 29)
  - Finance - Social Security - Nutritional Services for the Elderly (S. 2504) 1971 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Social Security - Optometric 1967-1970 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Social Security - Payments 1969-1970 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Social Security - Railroad Retirement 1967, 1970-1971 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Social Security - Training of Social Workers (S. 1150) 1967 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Social Security - Veterans 1967-1971, 4 folders (Box 29)
  - Finance - Taxes 1967-1972 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Taxes - Exemptions for Amateur Aircraft (H.R. 8731) 1971 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Taxes - Farmers 1969 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Taxes - Industrial Development Bonds 1969 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Taxes - Interstate Taxation 1968-1971 (Box 29)
  - Finance - Taxes - Investment Credit Tax 1967, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Finance - Taxes - Loopholes 1968 (Box 30)
  - Finance - Taxes - Overseas Travel 1968, 3 folders (Box 30)
  - Finance - Taxes - Revenue Sharing - the Heller Plan / Baker Bill 1965-1967 (Box 30)
  - Finance - Taxes - Surtax 1969, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Finance - Taxes - Tax Credit for Tuition 1967, 2 folders (Box 30)
  - Finance - Taxes - Tax Increase 1967-1968 Mar, 6 folders (Box 30)
  - Finance - Taxes - Tax Increase 1968 Apr-Nov, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Finance - Taxes - Tax Increase - Form Letter Reply 1967, 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Finance - Taxes - Tax Increase - Post Cards Supporting Passage of H.R. 15414 1968 (Box 31)
  - Finance - Taxes - Tax Surcharge Act Amendment (H.R. 2767) 1967-1968 (Box 31)
  - Finance - Tax Funds for Hospitals 1967 (Box 31)
  - Finance - Tax Reform 1969-1971, 13 folders (Box 31)
  - Finance - Tax Reform 1972, 3 folders (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Capital Gains Tax 1969 (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Charitable Gifts 1969, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Depletion Allowance 1969, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Investment Credit 1969 (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Municipal Bonds 1967-1969 (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Mutual Bonds 1969, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Non-Profit Organization 1968, 1972 (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Professional Corporations 1969 (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Profit Sharing & Pension Plans 1969 (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Single Person Tax 1969 (Box 32)
  - Finance - Tax Reform - Thank You Letters 1969-1970 (Box 32)
  - Finance - Trade Expansion - Kennedy Round 1966-1968, 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Finance - Unemployment Compensation Bill (H.R. 14705) 1970 (Box 32)
  - Finance - Welfare 1968-1972 (Box 32)
  - Foreign Relations 1965-1972, 20 folders (Box 33)
  - Foreign Relations - African Affairs 1967-1972 (Box 33)
  - Foreign Relations - African Affairs - Biafra 1968-1970, 2 folders (Box 34)
  - Foreign Relations - African Affairs - Congo 1967 (Box 34)
  - Foreign Relations - African Affairs - Rhodesia 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 34)
  - Foreign Relation - Dr. David F. Anthony Correspondence re Japan 1969-1970 (Box 34)
  - Foreign Relations - Arab-Israeli Conflict 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 34)
  - Foreign Relations - Arab-Israeli Conflict Telegrams 1967-1968, 4 folders (Box 34)
  - Foreign Relations - Arms Control & Disarmament 1968 (Box 34)
  - Foreign Relations - Atlantic Union 1972 (Box 34)
  - Foreign Relations - Cambodia 1970 Apr-May 11, 6 folders (Box 34)
  - Foreign Relations - Cambodia 1970 May 12-1971, 19 folders (Box 35)
  - Foreign Relations - Cambodia Petitions 1970, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - Cambodia Postcard Mail 1970 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - Cambodia Telegrams 1970, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - Canada 1971-1972 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - Canada Itinerary 1972 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - China 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - China - Admission to the United Nations 1971, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - China - Nixon's Visit 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - China - Printed Material 1968 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - China - Recognition by the United States 1971 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - Communism 1967 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - Cuba 1971 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - Department of Peace 1968-1969 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - Economic - Social Policy 1967 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs 1967-1972 (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - Consular Treaty with the U.S.S.R. 1967, 5 folders (Box 36)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - Czechoslovakia 1968 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - East-West Trade 1967 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - France 1968 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - France - Consular Treaty 1967 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - France - War Debt 1967 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - Glasboro Convention 1967 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - Greece 1967, 1971 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - Northern Ireland 1971-1972 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - Radio Free Europe 1967 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - European Affairs - Vatican Representative 1969 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - Foreign Aid 1967-1972, 8 folders (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - Fulbright S. Resolution 187 1969 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - Grievance System for Foreign Service Personnel, S.2023 1971 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - Illegal Drug Imports 1970-1972, 3 folders (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - International Grains Arrangement 1968 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - International Organizations 1967 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - Israel 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - Kennedy Round Tariffs 1967 (Box 37)
  - Foreign Relations - Korea & U.S.S. Pueblo 198-1969, 4 folders (Box 38)
  - Foreign Relations - Laos 1970 (Box 38)
  - Foreign Relations - Latin & South American Affairs 1969-1971 (Box 38)
  - Foreign Relations - Micronesia 1970 (Box 38)
  - Foreign Relations - Middle East 1968-1972, 12 folders (Box 38)
  - Foreign Relations - Middle East - Telegrams & Pamphlets 1970 (Box 38)
  - Foreign Relations - North Atlantic Treaty Organization 1968-1972, 3 folders (Box 38)
  - Foreign Relations - Nuclear Non-Proliferation 1968-1969, 4 folders (Box 39)
  - Foreign Relations - Okinawa 1969-1972 (Box 39)
  - Foreign Relations - Pakistan 1970-1971, 4 folders (Box 39)
  - Foreign Relations - Panama Canal 1967-1968, 1971-1972, 5 folders (Box 39)
  - Foreign Relations - Panama Canal (Form Letter Reply) 1967 (Box 39)
  - Foreign Relations - Pentagon Papers 1971 (Box 39)
  - Foreign Relations - Philippines 1969 (Box 39)
  - Foreign Relations - Strategic Arms Limitations Talks 1970-1972, 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Foreign Relations - South East Asia 1967-1971 Mar 15, 6 folders (Box 39)
  - Foreign Relations - South East Asia 1971 Mar 15-1972, 5 folders (Box 40)
  - Foreign Relations - Thailand 1967 (Box 40)
  - Foreign Relations - Treaties 1967-1968 (Box 40)
  - Foreign Relations - United Nations 1967-1972, 5 folders (Box 40)
  - Foreign Relations - United Nations - Genocide Convention 1970-1972, 6 folders (Box 40)
  - Foreign Relations - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics 1967-1970 (Box 40)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam 1967 Jan-Aug, 7 folders (Box 40)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam 1967 Sep-1969 Oct, 19 folders (Box 41)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam 1969 Nov-1972 May, 19 folders (Box 42)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam 1972 Jun-Nov, 10 folders (Box 43)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Case Church End the War Amendment S. 3526 1972 Apr-May, 10 folders (Box 43)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Case Church End the War Amendment S. 3526 1972 Jun, etc., 3 folders (Box 44)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Children in Vietnam 1971-1972, 3 folders (Box 44)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Conference of Asian Scholars 1968 (Box 44)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Congressional Record and Newsclippings 1967 (Box 44)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Con Son 1970 (Box 44)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Cooper-Church and McGovern-Hatfield Amendments S. 609 - Oppose Military Withdrawal 1970, 11 folders (Box 44)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Cooper-Church and McGovern-Hatfield Amendments S. 609 - Support Military Withdrawal 1970 May 1-20, 6 folders (Box 44)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Cooper-Church and McGovern-Hatfield Amendments S. 609 - Support Military Withdrawal 1970 May 21-Aug, 15 folders & 1 envelope (Box 45)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Foreign Aid 1967 (Box 45)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Goodell Bill S. 3000 1969 (Box 45)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam- President Johnson's Visit to the Church of Rev. Lewis & Reaction to Spong's Editorial re Visit 1967 (Box 45)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Mansfield Amendment 1971-1972, 5 folders (Box 45)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Oil Lease Hearings 1971 (Box 45)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Prisoners of War 1969-1970 May, 4 folders (Box 45)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Prisoners of War, etc. 1970 Jun-1972, 10 folders (Box 46)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Protests 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box 46)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Speech of Senator Robert Kennedy 1967 (Box 46)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - Supplemental Appropriations 1967 (Box 46)
  - Foreign Relations - Vietnam - War Powers 1971-1972, 2 folders (Box 46)
  - General 1966-1968 Jun, 10 folders (Box 46)
  - General 1968 Jul-1972, 20 folders (Box 47)
  - Government Operations 1967-1972, 4 folders (Box 48)
  - Government Operations - Alexandria Waterfront 1967-1971, Old King's Warehouse (Box 48)
  - Government Operations - Architectural and Engineering Firms, S. 3156, H.R. 12807 1972, 2 folders (Box 48)
  - Government Operations - Consumer Protection Agency (S. 3240) 1970 (Box 48)
  - Government Operations - Department of Peace 1969-1971 (Box 48)
  - Government Operations - Education Department (S. 1485) 1971 (Box 48)
  - Government Operations - Executive Reorganization 1972 (Box 48)
  - Government Operations - General Service Administrative Grantee Program 1972 (Box 48)
  - Government Operations - Intergovernmental Relations 1972 (Box 48)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs 1967-1972, 8 folders (Box 48)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Alaska Native Claims Settlement Act 1969-1972, 2 folders (Box 48)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Alaska Pipeline 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box 48)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Alaska Pipeline - Coast Guard Study 1972 (Box 48)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Animal Welfare, S. 1116 1971, 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Appropriations 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Appropriations - Arts & Humanities 1969-1970 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Deep Sea Mining (S. 2801) 1970-1972 (Box 49)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs - Dismal Swamp 1968-1971 (Box 49)